Now that we've downloaded, processed,
下载 处理
and then uploaded our data,
并上传数据后
it's time to start creating a model.
下面开始创建模型
As I mentioned in the last video,
正如我在上个视频中提到的
we're going to be using the XGBoost algorithm to create a model.
我们将使用 XGBoost 算法创建模型
Understanding how the XGBoost algorithm works
了解 XGBoost 算法的工作原理
is a little beyond the scope of this lesson.
已经超出了这节课的范畴
However, it's an important algorithm to have in your toolbox
但是 了解 XGBoost 算法很重要
as it is very effective when looking at tabular data.
因为处理表格数据的时候使用该算法很高效
In particular, it is one of the top performing algorithms used
它是在各种机器学习竞赛中
in various machine learning competitions such as those you might find on Kaggle.
效率排名靠前的算法 例如 Kaggle 竞赛中用到的算法
In order for stage maker to use XGBoost to fit a model,
为了让 StageMaker 使用 XGBoost 拟合模型
it needs to launch a virtual machine,
它需要启动虚拟机
would load the Docker container that we specify.
虚拟机将加载我们指定的 Docker 容器
Amazon provides an XGBoost docker container for us to use.
Amazon 向我们提供了 XGBoost Docker 容器
However, the name of the image depends on which region we are working in.
但是 镜像名称取决于我们所在的区域
Fortunately, there is a nice utility method
幸运的是 我们可以使用
called' get_ image_uri' that is provided by Amazon,
Amazon 提供的get_ image_uri 实用程序
that given the region name and the algorithm we want to use,
提供区域名称和要使用的算法后
creates the appropriate container name.
该实用程序将创建相应的容器名称
Once we have that, we can create
有了该名称之后 我们就可以
a sagemaker estimator object providing the name of the container we wish to use,
创建 StageMaker estimator 对象了 在这里提供要使用的容器名称
in our case, the XGBoost container,
对我们来说 即 XGBoost 容器
the role we are going to give this estimator,
并提供此 estimator 的角色
remember that a role tells Amazon what
角色可以告诉 Amazon
resources a particular object is allowed to access.
特定对象能够访问哪些资源
Since we want our estimator to access our training data,
因为我们希望 estimator 能访问训练数据
which is contained on s3,
训练数据存储在 S3 中
we have to make sure that our estimator has a role,
所以需要确保 estimator 具有
which allows access to s3.
能访问 S3 的角色
When we first created this notebook instance,
当我们一开始创建此 notebook 实例时
we give it a role that allowed it to access s3.
我们为其设定了可以访问 S3 的角色
So if we give our estimator the same
所以 如果为 estimator 设定的角色
role that this notebook instance has, we should be okay.
与此 notebook 实例的角色一样 就可以了
We also need to tell sagemaker how many instances,
我们还需要告诉 StageMaker 要创建多少个实例
that is how many virtual machines we want to create,
即要创建多少个虚拟机
in our case, one is fine,
对我们来说 是 1 个
and we need to tell sagemaker this instance or the virtual machine we want it to use.
我们需要告诉 StageMaker 我们要使用的实例或虚拟机类型
The ml. m4.xlarge instance type is perfectly fine for our uses.
ml.m4.xlarge 实例类型对我们来说就很合适
Lastly, we need to tell sagemaker where to store the final saved model.
最后 我们需要告诉 StageMaker 将最终保存的模型存储在哪里
In this case, we're going to save it to
我们将模型存储在默认存储桶中
the default_bucket in a folder that we set up before,
并放在之前设置的文件夹里
the prefix that we use previously.
即 prefix 指定的文件夹
Lastly, we need to provide the session object just in
最后 我们需要提供 session 对象
case sagemaker needs to use some additional information. All right.
以防 StageMaker 需要使用其他信息 好的
Now, we have an estimator object that has been created.
现在我们有了 estimator 对象
That estimator object is a wrapper for our XGBoost algorithm.
该 estimator 对象是 XGBoost 算法的封装器
Now, XGBoost itself has some hyperparameters that we can specify.
XGBoost 本身有一些超参数可以指定
For the most part, we're going to ignore what this mean,
我们可以忽略这些超参数的含义
but I would certainly encourage you to play around with
但是强烈建议你尝试不同的值
these values to see how it affects the model and how it fits the data.
看看这些值对模型及拟合数据有何影响
It is important to note that,
需要注意的是
because the median cost of a house is a floating point number,
因为房价中位数是浮点数
we want to use linear regression.
所以需要使用线性回归
Early stopping rounds is used by XGBoost to determine
XGBoost 利用 early_stopping_rounds 判断
whether or not it should complete it's processing of the data early.
是否提前结束数据处理
For example, if the model starts to do worse on the validation set,
例如 如果模型在验证集上性能开始下降
then we're probably overfitting and we should stop training the model.
那么我们可能过拟合了 应该停止训练模型
Lastly, we tell XGBoost the maximum number of rounds that we want it to iterate.
最后 我们告诉 XGBoost 最高迭代次数
Now that we've set the hyperparameters,
设置好超参数后
it's time to actually start fitting the model.
就可以开始拟合模型了
In order to fit the model,
在拟合模型时
the XGBoost estimator object has a handy function called fit,
XGBoost estimator 对象有一个很便利的函数 叫做 fit()
and all we need to do is provide it the location of
我们只需提供
the training data and the location of the validation data.
训练数据和验证数据的位置
Of course, that location is an object of its own,
当然 位置本身是一个对象
which describes not only where on s3 that data is located,
不仅描述了数据在 S3 上的位置
but also the format of the data.
而且描述了数据格式
In our case, the CSV files.
对我们来说 是 csv 文件
Now, we can watch as sagemaker requisitions our virtual machine,
现在等待 StageMaker 配置虚拟机
gets everything ready for it,
准备好一切
loads the image, and trains the model.
然后加载镜像和训练模型